drops the opening set,
输掉了首盘
but then steamrolls through the final two sets.
但随后在最后两盘一路横扫
一个6比3的开局
最后没能变成一场胜利
北京时间10月2日上午
中网女单第二轮
外卡参赛的袁悦
迎战4号种子安德烈耶娃
对手排名世界第5
Nicely done.
处理得漂亮
Put away there from Andreeva.
安德烈耶娃终结了这一分
追到边线外
袁悦用反手把低球救了回来
Oh, great shot from Yuan there.
哦 袁悦打出了一记好球
Excellent stuff.
真精彩
Had to go out wide to get that ball
她必须跑到很宽的位置去救球
and placed it nicely.
而且落点处理得很好
So, on serve to get
所以 开局双方都保住发球局
this second round matchup underway.
展开这场第二轮的较量
底线对拉中 袁悦不断变线
调动对手向两侧移动
首盘第六局
她在第五次机会完成破发
Oh, went the other way. Smart play.
哦 打向了另一边 聪明的选择
But she gets rewarded.
不过 她得到了回报
So, on her fifth opportunity,
所以 在第五次机会中
Yuan gets the first break
袁悦拿下了第一次破发
of the opening set.
是在这一场的首盘
袁悦首盘的一发赢分率接近69%
对手拿到4个破发点
她一个也没让出去
自己完成一次破发
6比3先赢一盘
And what a way to finish that opening set
这一球为首盘收尾 真是精彩
for Yuan Yue.
袁悦赢下首盘
And Mirra Andreeva, as you can tell,
可以看出 米拉 安德烈耶娃
disgusted.
非常懊恼
Throws the racket.
她摔了球拍
第二盘 袁悦的3个发球局全部失守
这一盘 她的一发赢分率降到45%
安德烈耶娃把大比分追平
No player has won more six-love sets
没有人赢下六比零的盘数更多
on tour this year than Mirra Andreeva.
本赛季巡回赛无人超过米拉
That's her 12th six-love set of 2026.
她在2026年的第12盘6比0
More importantly though, she's forced a third.
更重要的是 比赛进入决胜盘
后两盘 袁悦的6个发球局全丢了
3盘的一发赢分率逐盘下降
开局的领先没能坚持到最后
决胜盘 袁悦还是没能保住发球局
一发赢分率只剩27%
从先赢一盘到连丢12局 下一场
她能把首盘的主动进攻延续下去吗？
Oh, and it goes long.
哦 这一球出界了
And Mirra Andreeva drops the opening set,
米拉 安德烈耶娃首盘告负
but then steamrolls through the final two sets.
但随后在最后两盘一路横扫
Although that was a fun last point.
不过 最后这一分还是很精彩
Not many points won by Yuan Yue
袁悦赢下的分数并不多
in that last couple sets.
在最后这两盘中